<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Legio Marie</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Prayers</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Facts / More</item>
        <item>My Pages</item>
        <item>Handbook</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Fact_menu">
        <item>Object of the Legion</item>
        <item>Founder of the Legion</item>
        <item>Government of the Legion</item>
        <item>Membership of the Legion</item>
        <item>Spirit of the Legion  </item>
        <item>Events of the Legion</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@drawable/ic_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/praying_hands</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_photos</item>
        <item>@drawable/facts</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_pages</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_whats_hot</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="Prayer_menu">
        <item>Opening Prayers</item>
        <item>Rosary</item>
        <item>Litany Of Our Blessed Mother Mary</item>
        <item>The Catena Legionis</item>
        <item>Concluding Prayers</item>
        <item>Prayer to Saint Micheal The Archangel</item>
        <item>The Divine Praises</item>
        <item>The Little Crown of the Blessed Virgin Mary</item>
        <item>Prayer For Beatification of Frank Duff</item>
        <item>Prayer For Beatification of Alphonsus Lambe </item>
        <item>Prayer For Beatification of Edel Queen </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Prayers">
        <item>\b\t We make the Sign of the Cross saying.\t\n\b

In the name of the Father \nand of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.\n

Come, O Holy Spirit, fill the hearts of Your faithful, and enkindle in them the fire of Your love.\n
V>. Send forth Your Spirit, O Lord, and they shall be created.\n
R>. And You shall renew the face of the earth.\n
\t\t*****LET US PRAY.*****\t\t\n
 God our Father, pour out the gifts of Your Holy Spirit on the world.
You sent the Spirit on Your Church to begin the teaching of the gospel: 
now let the, Spirit continue to work in the world through the hearts of all who believe.
Through Christ our Lord. Amen.\n
V>. You, O Lord, will open my lips.\n
R>. And my tongue shall announce Your praise.\n
V>. Incline unto my aid, O God.\n
R>. O Lord, make haste to help me.\n
V>. Glory be to the Father, etc.\n
R>. As it was in the beginning, etc.\n
Then follow five decades of the Rosary.\n

\t\t*****SALVE REGINA*****\t\t\n

Hail, holy Queen, Mother of Mercy
hail, our life, our sweetness and our hope.
To you we cry, poor banished children of Eve,
to you we send up our sighs, mourning and weeping in this valley of tears.
Turn then, O most gracious advocate, your eyes of mercy towards us,
and after this our exile, show us the blessed fruit of your womb, Jesus.
O clement, \nO loving,\nO sweet Virgin Mary.\n
V>. Pray for us, O holy Mother of God.\n
R>. That we may be made worthy of the promises of Christ.\n


\t\t*****LET US PRAY.*****\t\t\n

O God, Whose only-begotten Son,by His life, death and resurrection,
has purchased for us the rewards of eternal salvation;
grant, we beseech You, that meditating upon these mysteries in the most holy 
Rosary of the Blessed Virgin Mary,
we may imitate what they contain, and obtain what they promise
Through the same Christ our Lord. Amen.\n
V>. Most Sacred Heart of Jesus\n
R>. Have mercy on us.\n
V>. Immaculate Heart of Mary\n
R>. Pray for us.\n
V>. St. Joseph\n
R>. Pray for us.\n
V>. St John the Evangelist\n
R>. Pray for us.\n
V>. St. Louis-Marie de Montfort\n
R>. Pray for us.\n
(We can conclude here by making the Sign of the Cross or continue on as time permits)\n
In the name of the Father, etc.\n</item>
        <item>\t\t*****OUR FATHER*****\t\t\n
            
V>.Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be Thy Name. Thy kingdom
come. Thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.\n
R>.Give us this day our daily bread, and forgive us our trespasses, as we
forgive those who trespass against us and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil. AMEN.\n
\t\t*****HAIL MARY*****\t\t\n
V>.Hail Mary, full of grace,the Lord is with thee.Blessed art thou among
women,and blessed is the Fruit of Thy womb Jesus.\n
R>.Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us, sinners, now and at the hour
of our death. AMEN.\n (10 times per mysteries)\n
\t\t*****GLORY BE*****\t\t\n
V>.Glory be to the Father, and the Son and to the Holy Spirit.\n
R>.As it was in the beginning, is now and ever shall be, world without end.
AMEN.\n
\t\t**MYSTERIES OF THE ROSARY**\t\n\t
\t****JOYFUL****\t\n
The Annunciation.\n
The Visitation.\n
The Birth of Jesus(Nativity).\n
The Presentation.\n
The Finding Jesus in the Temple.\n
\t****LUMINOUS****\t\n
The Baptism of Jesus.\n
The Miracle at the Wedding at Cana.\n
The Evangelization.\n
The Transfiguration.\n
The Institution of the Eucharist.\n
\t****SORROWFUL****\t\n
The Agony in the Garden.\n
The Scourging at the Pillar.\n
The Crowning with Thorns.\n
The Carrying of the Cross.\n
The Crucifixion and Death.\n
\t****GLORIOUS****\t\n
The Resurrection.\n
The Ascension.\n
The Descent of the Holy Spirit.\n
The Assumption.\n
The Coronation.\n</item>
        <item>           \t\t\tLITANY OF THE VIRGIN MARYn 
V>. Lord, have mercy on us.\n 
R>. Christ, have mercy on us.\n 
V>. Lord, have mercy on us. Christ hear us.\n 
R>. Christ,  graciously hear us.\n 
V>. God,  the Father of Heaven,\n 
R>. Have mercy on us.\n 
V>. God, the Son,  Redeemer of the world,\n 
V>. God, the Holy Spirit,\n 
V>. Holy Trinity,  One God,\n 
V>. Holy  Mary,\n 
R>. Pray For Us (till the end)\n 
V>. Holy Mother of God,\n 
V>. Holy Virgin of virgins,\n 
V>. Mother of Christ,\n
V>. Mother of divine grace,\n 
V>. Mother most pure,\n 
V>. Mother most chaste,\n 
V>. Mother inviolate,\n 
V>. Mother undefiled,\n 
V>. Mother most amiable,\n 
V>. Mother most admirable,\n 
V>. Mother of good counsel,\n 
V>. Mother of our Creator,\n 
V>. Mother of our Savior,\n 
V>. Virgin most prudent,\n 
V>. Virgin most venerable,\n 
V>. Virgin most renowned,\n 
V>. Virgin most powerful,\n 
V>. Virgin most merciful,\n 
V>. Virgin most faithful,\n 
V>. Mirror of justice,\n 
V>. Seat of wisdom,\n 
V>. Cause of our joy,\n 
V>. Spiritual vessel,\n 
V>. Vessel of honor,\n 
V>. Singular vessel of devotion,\n 
V>. Mystical rose,\n 
V>. Tower of David,\n 
V>. Tower of ivory,\n 
V>. House of gold,\n 
V>. Ark of the covenant,\n 
V>. Gate of Heaven,\n 
V>. Morning star,\n 
V>. Health of the sick,\n 
V>. Refuge of sinners,\n 
V>. Comforter of the afflicted,\n 
V>. Help of Christians,\n 
V>. Queen of Angels,\n 
V>. Queen of Patriarchs,\n 
V>. Queen of Prophets,\n 
V>. Queen of Apostles,\n 
V>. Queen of Martyrs,\n 
V>. Queen of Confessors,\n 
V>. Queen of Virgins,\n 
V>. Queen of all Saints,\n 
V>. Queen conceived without Original Sin,\n 
V>. Queen assumed into Heaven,\n 
V>. Queen of the most holy rosary,\n 
V>. Queen of Peace,\n 
V>. Queen of the family,\n 
V>. Lamb of God, who takes away the sins of the world, \n
R>. Spare us O Lord.\n
V>. Lamb of God, who takes away the sins of the world, \n
R>. Graciously hear us O Lord.\n
V>. Lamb of God, who takes away the sins of the world, \n
R>. Have mercy on us.\n
V>. Pray for us, O holy Mother of God. \n
R>. That we may be made worthy of the promises of Christ.\n
\t\t\tLet us pray:\n
Pour forth, we beseech you O Lord, your grace into our hearts, that we, to whom the Incarnation of Christ, your Son was made
known by the message of an angel, may by His Passion and Cross be brought to the glory of His Resurrection; through the same Christ our Lord.
AMEN.</item>
        <item>   \t\t V>.Antiphon. Who is she that comes forth as the morning 
rising\n
R>.Fair as the moon, bright as the sun, terrible as an army
set in battle array?\n
V>.My soul glorifies the Lord,\n
R>.my spirit rejoices in God, my Saviour.\n
V>.He looks on his servant in her lowliness;\n
R>.henceforth all ages will call me blessed.\n
V>.The Almighty works marvels for me.\n
R>.Holy his name!\n
V>.His mercy is from age to age,\n
R>.on those who fear him.\n
V>.He puts forth his arm in strength\n
R>.and scatters the proud-hearted.\n
V>.He casts the mighty from their thrones\n
R>.and raises the lowly.\n
V>.He fills the starving with good things,\n
R>.sends the rich away empty.\n
V>.He protects Israel, his servant,\n
R>.remembering his mercy,\n
V>.The mercy promised to our fathers,\n
R>.to Abraham and his sons for ever.\n
V>.Glory be to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy
Spirit.\n
R>.As it was in the beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world
without end, Amen.\n
V>.Antiphon. Who is she that comes forth as the morning
rising, fair as the moon, bright as the sun, terrible as an army
set in battle array?\n
V/. O Mary, conceived without sin.\n
R/. Pray for us who have recourse to you.\n
\t\t\tLet us pray\n
O Lord Jesus Christ, our mediator with the Father, you have
been pleased to appoint the most Blessed Virgin, your Mother,
to be our mother also, and our mediatrix with you, mercifully
grant that whoever comes to you seeking your favours may
rejoice to receive all of them through her. Amen.</item>
        <item>   \t\t In the name of the Father \n
We fly to your patronage, O Holy Mother of God; despise
not our prayers in our necessities, but ever deliver us from all
dangers, O glorious and blessed Virgin.\n
V/. (Invocation appropriate to praesidium)\n
 R/. Pray for us.\n

V/. Mary Immaculate, Mediatrix of all Graces \n
R/. Pray for us.\n
V/. St. Michael and St. Gabriel\n
 R/. Pray for us.\n
V/. All you heavenly Powers, Mary’s Legion
of Angels \n
R/. Pray for us.\n
V/. St. John the Baptist\n
 R/. Pray for us.\n
V/. Saints Peter and Paul\n
 R/. Pray for us.\n
The following is to be said in unison down to the first Amen;
after that by the priest.\n
\t\tConfer,\n O Lord, on us,
Who serve beneath the standard of Mary,
That fullness of faith in you and trust in her,
To which it is given to conquer the world.
Grant us a lively faith, animated by charity,
Which will enable us to perform all our actions
From the motive of pure love of you,
And ever to see you and serve you in our neighbour;
A faith, firm and immovable as a rock,
Through which we shall rest tranquil and steadfast
Amid the crosses, toils and disappointments of life;
A courageous faith which will inspire us
To undertake and carry out without hesitation
Great things for your glory and for the salvation of souls;
A faith which will be our Legion’s Pillar of Fire
To lead us forth united 
To kindle everywhere the fires of divine love
To enlighten those who are in darkness and in the shadow
of death
To inflame those who are lukewarm
To bring back life to those who are dead in sin;
And which will guide our own feet in the way of peace;

So that  the battle of life over 
Our Legion may reassemble,
Without the loss of any one,
In the kingdom of your love and glory. Amen.
May the souls of our departed legionaries
And the souls of all the faithful departed
Through the mercy of God rest in peace. Amen.\n
In the name of the Father\n</item>
        <item>\t
Saint Michael the Archangel, defend us in battle. Be our safeguard against the wickedness and snares of the devil. May God rebuke him, we
humbly pray; and do thou, O Prince of the Heavenly Host, by the Power of God, cast into hell satan and all the evil spirits, who prowl about the
world seeking the ruin of souls. AMEN.</item>
        <item>\t
Blessed be God.\n
Blessed be His Holy Name.\n
Blessed be Jesus Christ, True God and True Man.\n
Blessed be the Name of Jesus.\n
Blessed be His Most Sacred Heart.\n
Blessed be His Most Precious Blood.\n
Blessed be Jesus in the Most Holy Sacrament of the Altar.\n
Blessed be the Holy Spirit, the Paraclete.\n
Blessed be the Great Mother of God, Mary Most Holy.\n
Blessed be her Holy and Immaculate Conception.\n
Blessed be her Glorious Assumption.\n
Blessed be the Name of Mary, Virgin and Mother.\n
Blessed be Saint Joseph, her most Chaste Spouse.\n
Blessed be God in His Angels and in His Saints.\n
May the Heart of Jesus, in the Most Blessed Sacrament, be praised, adored and loved with grateful affection, at every moment, in all the
tabernacles of the world, even to the end of time.\n AMEN.</item>
        <item>           \tIntroductory Prayer\n

Come Holy Spirit, fill the hearts of Thy faithful and enkindle winthin them the fire of Thy love\n
V. Send forth Thy Spirit and they shall be created.\n
R. And Thou shalt renew the face of the earth.\n
Let us pray.\n
O God, Who by the light of the Holy Spirit dost instruct the hearts of\n
the faithful, grant us by this same Spirit to relish what is right and\n
ever to rejoice in His consolation, through Jesus Christ, our Lord. Amen.\n

\t\tI. Crown of Excellence\n

(To honor the Divine Maternity of the Blessed Virgin, her ineffable Virginity,
her purity without stain and her innumerable virtues.)\n

\t1. Our Father, Hail Mary.\n
Blessed art thou, O Virgin Mary, who didst bear the Lord, the Creator of the world;
thou didst give birth to Him Who made thee, and remainest a Virgin forever.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t2. Hail Mary.\n
O holy and immaculate Virgin, I know not with what praise to extol thee, 
since thou didst bear in thy womb the very One Whom the Heavens cannot contain.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t3. Hail Mary.\n
Thou are all fair, O Virgin Mary, and there is no stain in thee.
Rejoice, O Virgin Maryd; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t4. Hail Mary.
Thy virtues, O Virgin, surpass the stars in number.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!
Glory be to the Father.\n

\tII. Crown of Power\n

(To honor the royalty of the Blessed Virgin, her magnificence, her universal mediation and the strength of her rule.)
\n
\t5. Our Father, Hail Mary.\n
Glory be to thee, O Empress of the world! Bring us with thee to the joys of Heaven.
Rejoice, O Virgin Maryd; Rejoice a thousand times!\n
6. Hail Mary.\n
Glory be to thee, O treasure house of the Lord\'s graces! Grant us a share in thy riches.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t7. Hail Mary.
Glory be to thee, O Mediatrix between God and man! Through thee may the Almighty be favorable to us.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t8. Glory be to thee who destroyest heresies and crushest demons!
Be thou our loving guide.
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n
Glory be to the Father.\n

\tGlory be to the Father.\n

\tIII. Crown of Goodness\n

(To honor the mercy of the Blessed Virgin toward sinners, the poor, the just and the dying.)\n

\t9. Our Father, Hail Mary.\n

Glory be to thee, O refuge of sinners! Intercede for us with God.\n
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t10. Hail Mary.\n
Glory be to thee, O Mother of orphans! Render the Almighty favorable to us.\n
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!

\t11. Hail Mary.\n
Glory be to thee, O joy of the just! Lead us with thee to the joys of Heaven.\n
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n

\t12. Hail Mary.\n
Glory be to thee who are ever ready to assist us in life and death! Lead us with thee to the kingdom of Heaven!\n
Rejoice, O Virgin Mary; Rejoice a thousand times!\n
Glory be to the Father.\n

\tConcluding Prayer\n

\tLet Us Pray.\n

Hail, Mary, Daughter of God the Father\n
Hail, Mary, Mother of God the Son\n
Hail, Mary, Spouse of the Holy Ghost\n
Hail, Mary, Temple of the most Holy Trinity\n
Hail, Mary, my Mistress, my treasure, my joy, Queen of my heart; my Mother, 
my life, my sweetness, my dearest hope 
yea, my heart and my soul! 
I am all thine and all that I have is Thine,
O Virgin blessed above all things!
 Let thy soul be in me to magnify the Lord;
 let thy spirit be in me to rejoice in God.
 Set thyself, O faithful Virgin,
  as a seal upon my heart,
  that in thee and through thee I may be found faithful to God. 
  Receive me, O gracious Virgin,
  among those whom thou lovest and teachest,
  whom thou leadest, nourishest and protectest as thy children. 
  Grant that for love of thee I may despise all 
  earthly consolations and ever cling to those of Heaven until,
   through thee, His faithful spouse,
 Jesus Christ thy Son be formed in me for the glory of the Father.\n</item>
        <item>\t\t \tGod our Father,

You inspired your servant Frank Duff
 with a profound insight into the mystery 
 of your Church, the Body of Christ, 
 and of the place of Mary the Mother of Jesus in this mystery.
In his immense desire to share this insight with others 
and in filial dependence on Mary he formed her Legion 
to be a sign of her maternal love for the world and a means 
of enlisting all her children in the Church\'s evangelizing work.
We thank you Father for the graces conferred 
on him and for the benefits accruing to the Church 
from his courageous and shining faith.
With confidence we beg you that through his 
intercession you grant the petition we lay before you.(Say your Petitions)
We ask too that if it be in accordance with your will, 
the holiness of his life may be acknowledged by
the Church for the glory of your Name, through Christ Our Lord,\n Amen.</item>
        <item>\t \t \tGod, who by your infinite mercy
inflamed the heart of your servant,
Alphonsus Lambe with an ardent love for
you and for Mary, our Mother;a love which
revealed itself in a life of intense labour,
prayer and sacrifice for the salvation of
souls, grant, if it be your will,that we may
obtain, by his intercession, what we cannot
obtain by our own merits. We ask this
through Jesus Christ, Our Lord.\n Amen</item>
        <item>    \t \t \tEternal Father\n, I thank you for the grace you gave
to your servant, Edel Quinn, of striving to live
always in the joy of your presence, for the radiant
charity infused into her heart by your Holy Spirit,
and for the strength she drew from the Bread of
Life to labour until death for the glory of your
name, in loving dependence on Mary, Mother of the Church.
Confident, O Merciful Father, that her life was
pleasing to you,I beg you to grant me, through her
intercession, the special favour I now implore.(Say your Petitions),
and to make known by miracles the glory she
enjoys in Heaven, so that she may be glorified also
by your Church on earth, through Christ Our Lord.\n
Amen</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>
    <string name="title_activity_content_fragment">ContentFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_frag">TestFrag</string>

    <color name="dark_grey">#696969</color>

    <string name="Open_Book_1">Open Book 1</string>
    <string name="Open_Book_2">Open Book 2</string>
    <string name="Enable_Parallel_Texts">Enable Parallel Texts</string>
    <string name="Toggle_Sync_Views">Toggle Sync Views</string>
    <string name="Reset_Sync_Views">Reset Sync Views</string>
    <string name="Show_Metadata">Show Metadata</string>
    <string name="Refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="From_Book_1">From Book 1</string>
    <string name="From_Book_2">From Book 2</string>
    <string name="Sync_Book_1_with_Book_2">Sync Book 1 with Book 2</string>
    <string name="Sync_Book_2_with_Book_1">Sync Book 2 with Book 1</string>
    <string name="Book_1">Book 1</string>
    <string name="Book_2">Book 2</string>
    <string name="bookOpen">bookOpen</string>
    <string name="Table_of_Contents">Table of Contents</string>
    <string name="Change_Size">Change Panel Size</string>
    <string name="error_LoadPage">Can not load the page</string>
    <string name="error_LoadBook">Cannot load the book</string>
    <string name="error_onlyOneBookOpen">Only one book open!</string>
    <string name="error_cannotSynchronize">Cannot synchronize!</string>
    <string name="error_metadataNotFound">Metadata not found!</string>
    <string name="error_tocNotFound">Table of Contents not Found!</string>
    <string name="error_cannotChangeSizes">Can not change sizes!</string>
    <string name="url">url</string>
    <string name="bpath">bpath</string>
    <string name="invisible">invisible</string>
    <string name="second">second</string>
    <string name="time">time</string>
    <string name="error_cannotTurnPage">Cannot turn Page!</string>
    <string name="tome">tome</string>
    <string name="lang">lang</string>
    <string name="error_noOtherLanguages">No other languages!</string>
    <string name="state">state</string>
    <string name="error_cannotLoadState">Cannot load the application/book state</string>
    <string name="textOrHTML">text/html</string>
    <string name="sync">sync</string>
    <string name="page">page</string>
    <string name="CurrentPageBook">CurrentPageBook</string>
    <string name="LanguageBook">LanguageBook</string>
    <string name="pathBook">pathBook</string>
    <string name="error_CannotCloseStream">Cannot close stream!</string>
    <string name="Book_Stream">Book Stream</string>
    <string name="nameEpub">nameEpub</string>
    <string name="error_goToPage">goToPage error:</string>
    <string name="full_path">full-path</string>
    <string name="zip">.zip</string>
    <string name="htmlBodyTableOpen">&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;table&gt;</string>
    <string name="titlesMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Titles:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="authorsMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Authors:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="contributorsMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Contributors:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="languageMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Language:&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;</string>
    <string name="publishersMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Publishers:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="typesMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Types:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="descriptionsMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Descriptions:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="rightsMeta">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Rights:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="tablebodyhtmlClose">&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</string>
    <string name="tocReference">&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Table of Contents:&lt;/td&gt;</string>
    <string name="change_Font">Change Font</string>
    <string name="change_Font_Color">Font Color:</string>
    <string name="changeStyle">Change Style</string>
    <string name="blue_rgb">#0000ff</string>
    <string name="red_rgb">#ff0000</string>
    <string name="green_rgb">#00ff00</string>
    <string name="black_rgb">#000000</string>
    <string name="white_rgb">#ffffff</string>
    <string name="error_CannotChangeStyle">Cannot Change Style!</string>
    <string name="OK">OK</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="SetSizeTitle">Upper Panel Size:</string>
    <string name="LanguageChooserTitle">Choose two languages:</string>
    <string name="parallelTextBool">parallelTextBool</string>

    <string-array name="ColorFont">
        <item>Black</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>White</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="ChangeBackgroundColor">Background Color:</string>

    <string-array name="ColorBack">
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Black</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="syncScroll">Sync. Scroll</string>
    <string name="ChangeFont">Font:</string>

    <string-array name="FontStyle">
        <item>Sans Serif</item>
        <item>Serif</item>
        <item>Monospace</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Arial">Sans Serif</string>
    <string name="Serif">Serif</string>
    <string name="Monospace">Monospace</string>
    <string name="FontSize">Font Size:</string>
    <string name="LineHeight">Line Height:</string>
    <string name="TextAlign">Alignment:</string>

    <string-array name="testAlignOption">
        <item>Left</item>
        <item>Center</item>
        <item>Right</item>
        <item>Justify</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Left_Align">Left</string>
    <string name="Center_Align">Center</string>
    <string name="Right_Align">Right</string>
    <string name="DefaultSettings">Default</string>
    <string name="px">px</string>
    <string name="open">Open...</string>
    <string name="Margin">Margin(px):</string>

    <string-array name="FontSize">
        <item>100%</item>
        <item>125%</item>
        <item>150%</item>
        <item>175%</item>
        <item>200%</item>
        <item>90%</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="LineHeight">
        <item>1em</item>
        <item>1.25em</item>
        <item>1.5em</item>
        <item>1.75em</item>
        <item>2em</item>
        <item>0.9em</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Justify">Justify</string>

    <string-array name="Margin">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_split_panel">SplitPanel</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_book_view">BookView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tocview">TOCView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_data_view">DataView</string>
    <string name="ViewType">ViewType</string>
    <string name="title_activity_audio_view">AudioView</string>
    <string name="audio">Extract Audio</string>
    <string name="error_openaudiofile">Cannot open audio file</string>
    <string name="play">&gt;</string>
    <string name="pause">| |</string>
    <string name="rew">&lt;&lt;</string>
    <string name="exAudio">exAudio</string>
    <string name="no_audio">Can\'t find any audio file</string>
    <string name="title_activity_prayer_detail">PrayerDetail</string>

</resources>